Website: www.dannoot.tech

Email: khoa_dang_nguyen@hotmail.com

Danny Nguyen

(i.e. Dang Khoa Nguyen)

Adelaide, South Australia +61 434 588 098

SUMMARY

I am a self-motivated and enthusiastic Mechatronic Engineer Graduate with 1 year of work experience at Supashock Advanced Technologies. Currently seeking a graduate role opportunity within the engineering industry that will allow me to learn and apply my academic learnings and complement theory with practice.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Supashock Advanced Technologies

Graduate Role

November 2022 - Current

- Designed Mechanical Solutions using NX Siemens for the Anti-Tank Guided Missile (ATGM). Produced engineering drawings for manufactured machine parts and wiring harnesses.
- Designed Tooling and Jigs for the assembly of the ATGM, decreasing production assembly cost by 9%
- Developed wiring harness solutions within the ATGM, utilising military-grade connectors, backshells, boots and wiring.
- Organised and managed Bills of Materials and Assembly Instructions, leading to 15% price reduction.
- Coordinated between design and production team to ensure end product meets client specifications and Australian Defense Force Standards.

PREVIOUS PROJECTS

Anti-Tank Guided Missile

November 2022 – Current

The Anti-Tank Guided Missile project is a collaboration between Supashock Advanced Technologies and Rheinmetall to produce a retractable turret-mounted launcher for the Spike LR2 Anti-Tank Guided Missile.

Integrating VR environment with a Stewart Platform

March 2022 – *November* 2022

This project involves the development of a Lunar Rover Simulation utilizing a Stewart Platform, Racing Simulator and VR Headset. Throughout the project, programming of a Unity Engine script to extract kinematic data, integration between all devices and manufacturing of safety equipment were completed.

Computational Fluid Dynamics on a Submarine

March 2022 - June 2022

This project studies the drag coefficient on different nose designs on the hull of Collin's class submarine using Computational Fluid Dynamics.

Finite Element Analysis on a Bird Strike

March 2021 - June 2021

This project investigates Finite Element Methods (FEA) in the analysis of bird strike impacts upon the Cessna 172 wing air foil.

Designing an autonomous weather station

July 2020 – November 2020

This project focuses on the design of an autonomous weather station in terms of a client's needs. Surviving the harsh environments of the arctic and providing accurate data on the wind speed/direction, temperature, snow depth and precipitation.

EDUCATION

The University of Adelaide

Graduating in August 2023

Bachelor of Engineering (Honours) (Mechatronics) | GPA 4.74

Blackfriars Priory School

South Australian Certificate of Education | ATAR 89.96

- All Years High / Highest Honours for yearly academic reports
- Strong presence in the sporting community through being member of the aquatic and badminton teams.

Skills

- Proficient in MATLAB/Simulink, Solidworks/Inventor/Siemens NX CAD, Ansys FEA, Ansys CFD, C/C++, Latex, Microsoft Word/Excel, Mac OSX, Windows.
- Familiar with HTML, CSS, Java, Python, Solidity, Festos, circuit design.
- Bilingual; English and Vietnamese